<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-06-04T14:57:57+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Embracing Authenticity</title><subtitle>A space to grow, reflect, and be your true self.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Trusting the Process: When Good Decisions Still Hurt</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/trusting-the-process-good-decisions-still-hurt/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trusting the Process: When Good Decisions Still Hurt" /><published>2025-06-04T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-06-04T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/trusting-the-process-good-decisions-still-hurt</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/trusting-the-process-good-decisions-still-hurt/"><![CDATA[<p>Body:</p>

<p>Sometimes, poker doesn’t punish bad decisions.
Sometimes, it punishes good ones.</p>

<p>We were six-handed in an $88 tournament. I had 40 big blinds in the small blind. The button min-raised, and I flatted with pocket nines.</p>

<p>Now, the big blind — sitting on a 10 big blind stack — shoved all in.</p>

<p>It folded back to the button, and he reshoved. All in. Forty bigs.</p>

<p>Now here’s where the spot gets interesting.</p>

<p>I’d underrepresented my hand by just calling preflop. From the button’s perspective, I likely looked capped — maybe like I had a weak suited ace, some middling connectors, or a hand I didn’t want to 3-bet. And so, when the BB jams for 10BB, the button has every reason to isolate wide. I think his range includes:</p>

<p>Small pairs (22–88)</p>

<p>Broadways like ATo+, AJo+, KQo</p>

<p>Suited aces and connectors</p>

<p>And of course, value hands — TT+</p>

<p>In other words, his iso-jam range is wide.</p>

<p>So I called with 99, thinking I’m ahead of most of that.</p>

<p>And I was.</p>

<p>The big blind had pocket eights.
The board ran out 8-9-10.
Flopped middle set. But it didn’t hold.</p>

<p>It’s easy to feel stupid after a hand like that. Easy to doubt myself.</p>

<p>But when I step back and take emotion out of it — the analysis holds.</p>

<p>Flatting pre with 99 isn’t wrong. It’s balanced.</p>

<p>BB’s 10BB shove is standard.</p>

<p>Button’s iso range should be wide given my perceived weakness.</p>

<p>Calling with 99 against that range is profitable.</p>

<p>I made the right call.
It just didn’t work out this time.</p>

<hr />

<p>That’s the hardest part of poker — separating decision quality from outcome.</p>

<p>But it’s also the most important.</p>

<p>This hand didn’t teach me that I misplayed.
It taught me that I’m learning to trust myself, even when the board doesn’t go my way.</p>

<p>Because sometimes good decisions still hurt.
And that’s okay.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Poker," /><category term="Decision-Making," /><category term="Mindset," /><category term="Variance," /><category term="Emotional" /><category term="Regulation" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A reflection on a tough poker hand that reminds me why trusting sound logic — not results — is the real mark of growth.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Safety of the Unavailable</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/the-safety-of-the-unavailable/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Safety of the Unavailable" /><published>2025-06-04T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-06-04T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/the-safety-of-the-unavailable</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/the-safety-of-the-unavailable/"><![CDATA[<p>There’s something oddly comforting about women who are unavailable.</p>

<p>Maybe they’re married. Maybe they’re distant. Maybe they’ve made it clear — they’re not interested.<br />
And yet, somehow, that’s where I’ve felt most able to be… me.</p>

<p>Because there’s no risk of intimacy when intimacy is off the table.<br />
No threat of being fully seen, only to be fully rejected.<br />
No possibility of things going somewhere, which means no chance of them falling apart.</p>

<p>That’s not manipulative. That’s a nervous system seeking safety.</p>

<p>And it’s only now that I’m starting to understand it — not judge it.</p>

<hr />

<p>I’ve felt attraction to women I can’t have, and I’ve also felt shame about it.<br />
But when I sit with that shame — when I ask what’s really underneath — I don’t find bad intentions.<br />
I find unmet needs.</p>

<p>A desire to feel wanted.<br />
A longing to be seen, but only from a safe distance.<br />
A craving for connection without the risk of abandonment.</p>

<hr />

<p>There’s a younger part of me in all of this.<br />
The boy who grew up being hurt by closeness.<br />
The one who learned that love wasn’t safe, and that wanting something — especially someone — often led to pain.</p>

<p>That part of me doesn’t need to be fixed.<br />
He needs to be listened to.<br />
He needs to know he’s not dirty or shameful for wanting to feel something, even if it’s been misdirected.</p>

<hr />

<p>I want to change this pattern — not because desiring someone is wrong — but because I want to stop running from real intimacy.<br />
I want to desire women who can meet me where I’m at.<br />
I want to be seen — not just glimpsed from afar.</p>

<p>And maybe the first step is letting myself be seen… by me.</p>

<p>Even in the places that feel a bit messy.<br />
Even in the places where shame whispers that I’m too much.</p>

<p>Maybe especially there.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Healing," /><category term="Desire," /><category term="Vulnerability," /><category term="Shame," /><category term="Relationships" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring why I feel safer around unavailable women, and what that says about the intimacy I fear and the connection I crave.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Pull to Do, and the Practice of Being</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/the-pull-to-do-and-the-practice-of-being/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Pull to Do, and the Practice of Being" /><published>2025-06-04T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-06-04T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/the-pull-to-do-and-the-practice-of-being</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/the-pull-to-do-and-the-practice-of-being/"><![CDATA[<p>I noticed today how hard it is to just <em>sit with myself.</em></p>

<p>My dog was lying on me. It was peaceful. Safe. And still, I felt that tug — the familiar pull toward <em>doing</em>. Play poker. Work on the website. Be productive.</p>

<p>Even though poker is a game, it still carries that sense of “progress.” Something I can <em>win</em> at. Something I can <em>achieve</em>. It doesn’t matter how exhausted I am — my mind equates stillness with failure. With being lazy. With being <em>less</em>.</p>

<p>But the truth is: sitting with myself is one of the hardest, most courageous things I’ve ever tried to do.<br />
Because in that stillness, all the parts of me I’ve ignored begin to speak.<br />
And I realise how much of my life has been spent trying to outrun them.</p>

<p>My dog eventually moved away — chose the floor instead. And it stirred something. That small ache of aloneness. Not dramatic. Just a shift. Enough for my nervous system to say, <em>You’re alone again. Time to get busy.</em></p>

<p>But I wasn’t alone. I was with <em>me</em>.</p>

<p>And maybe that’s the real work now.<br />
Not pushing through.<br />
Not fixing myself.<br />
Just being with myself — especially in those quiet moments when there’s “nothing” to do.</p>

<p>Because that’s when I’m learning:<br />
I am not what I produce.<br />
I don’t have to earn rest.<br />
I don’t have to <em>do</em> to be <em>enough.</em></p>

<p>Sometimes the bravest thing I can do is simply… <em>be here</em>.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Presence," /><category term="Self-Compassion," /><category term="Anxiety," /><category term="Stillness," /><category term="Nervous" /><category term="System" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A reflection on the quiet discomfort of doing nothing and learning to feel safe in simply being.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Pity Friendship and the Right to Stand Equal</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/the-pity-friendship-and-the-right-to-stand-equal/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Pity Friendship and the Right to Stand Equal" /><published>2025-06-04T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-06-04T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/the-pity-friendship-and-the-right-to-stand-equal</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/the-pity-friendship-and-the-right-to-stand-equal/"><![CDATA[<p>Body:</p>

<p>I’ve just realised something hard to admit, but freeing.</p>

<p>There was a friendship in my life — one that lasted over 15 years — that I think was never truly equal. It was likely held together by something that looked like care, but wasn’t really connection.</p>

<p>The other person had lost people to suicide. I think they might have felt good — even righteous — about helping someone like me. Maybe they saw me as someone fragile, someone to protect. And at times, I was fragile.</p>

<p>But I wasn’t on their level. Not in their eyes. And deep down, I think I knew that.
And I accepted it.</p>

<p>Because I wanted to be looked after. I was drawn to people who would take that role — people who made me feel safe, even if it meant being the one always a little bit behind, always a little less.</p>

<p>Looking back now, I see how human that was. I needed safety. I needed someone. But I also see how that dynamic — when sustained over years — kept me small. It might not have been intentional on their part, but when someone is always “helping” you, there’s a subtle imbalance of power that develops. One that can be hard to escape.</p>

<p>And I’ve resented people for that.
Still do, if I’m honest.
But I also see now — that resentment isn’t the whole story.</p>

<p>Because I played a part too.</p>

<p>Not in creating the dynamic — but in maintaining it.
I didn’t know better. But now I do.</p>

<hr />

<p>This in-between period I’m in?
This space without the old friends, without the distractions, without the illusion of safety?</p>

<p>It’s been necessary. Painfully, quietly, beautifully necessary.
Because I could have gone through life continuing the same cycles. And on the surface, everything would have looked fine.</p>

<p>But I would have never met myself.
Never claimed my full weight in the world.
Never stepped into the kind of relationship where I could stand equal — not pitied, not rescued, not admired — just seen.</p>

<p>And that is my birthright.
To be whole.
To be loved without hierarchy.
To be a friend, not a project.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Healing," /><category term="Friendship," /><category term="Boundaries," /><category term="Self-Worth," /><category term="Personal" /><category term="Growth" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years I stayed in a friendship that made me feel safe but small. I see now that it was never equal — and that healing means stepping into the relationships where I can finally stand tall.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Longing to Be Desired</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/the-longing-to-be-desired/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Longing to Be Desired" /><published>2025-06-04T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-06-04T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/the-longing-to-be-desired</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/the-longing-to-be-desired/"><![CDATA[<p>There’s a part of me I don’t often talk about.</p>

<p>The part that longs to be desired — not just liked, not just accepted — but <em>truly wanted</em>. The kind of desire that doesn’t just tolerate your presence but lights up at the sight of you. That leans in. That lingers.</p>

<p>For a long time, I told myself I didn’t need that. That I was above it, or beyond it, or better off without it. But that wasn’t the truth. That was the survival story I had to write when I wasn’t being mirrored back as worthy. When desire felt unsafe. When I associated wanting with rejection.</p>

<p>So I suppressed it.<br />
And in its place, I became “nice.”<br />
I became “safe.”<br />
I became someone who could never be rejected — but also, someone who rarely got to be fully seen.</p>

<p>Recently, I’ve started to realise that this part of me — the part that wants to feel <em>wanted</em> — isn’t weak. It’s not shameful. It’s not manipulative or selfish.<br />
It’s sacred.</p>

<p>It’s the part of me that still believes intimacy could be mutual. That someone could see me — <em>truly</em> see me — and not flinch. That desire could exist without danger. That I wouldn’t be abandoned for being too much, or shamed for being vulnerable, or punished for being real.</p>

<p>That feels like healing.</p>

<p>And yes, it’s scary.<br />
Yes, I still feel the echoes of old wounds.<br />
But I’m starting to notice: the more I allow myself to feel that desire — without judgment — the more human I feel. The more whole I feel.</p>

<p>This isn’t about rushing into connection. It’s not about needing someone to fill a gap. It’s about reclaiming a part of myself I once buried to survive.</p>

<p>I want to be desired.<br />
And that’s okay.</p>

<p>Maybe you do too.<br />
And maybe it’s time we stop pretending otherwise.</p>

<hr />

<p><em>Sometimes the most radical thing we can do is admit we want to be wanted — and then, lovingly, want ourselves first.</em></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Desire," /><category term="Shame," /><category term="Healing," /><category term="Self-Acceptance," /><category term="Vulnerability" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring the quiet ache of wanting to be desired — and why it’s not something to be ashamed of.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Searching for the Nurturing Parent — And Finding the Critical One</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/searching-for-the-nurturing-parent/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Searching for the Nurturing Parent — And Finding the Critical One" /><published>2025-06-04T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-06-04T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/searching-for-the-nurturing-parent</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/searching-for-the-nurturing-parent/"><![CDATA[<p>Body:</p>

<p>I’ve started to see a pattern that has run through most of my relationships.</p>

<p>At some level, I think I’ve been searching for a part of myself in other people — the part that was never fully met in childhood. The nurturing parent. The one who sees me gently, holds space, offers warmth without judgment.</p>

<p>But instead of that, I often ended up with the critical parent — the voice that judges, corrects, stands one step above.
And I took the one-down position.
Again and again.</p>

<p>It’s not always obvious.
Sometimes the relationship even feels healthy on the surface.
But when I look closely, the dynamic is still there — that sense that I’m the one being helped, tolerated, subtly managed.</p>

<hr />

<p>And the truth is…
On some level, I wanted that.</p>

<p>Not the criticism, but the care. The containment. The feeling that someone could finally give me what I missed.</p>

<p>Of course I looked for it in others.
Of course I kept ending up in uneven dynamics.
Because I’d never known what it felt like to be held without hierarchy.</p>

<hr />

<p>For a long time, I denied how bad my childhood really was.
How little attunement there was.
How unskilled my parents were at parenting.</p>

<p>And because I couldn’t face that, I internalised all the shame of it.
I believed it was me. That I was too much. Too sensitive. Too needy.</p>

<p>But it wasn’t me.
The shame didn’t start in me. It was passed to me — by parents who couldn’t meet my needs, and then made me feel wrong for having them.</p>

<p>And I’ve been carrying that shame into relationships ever since.</p>

<hr />

<p>But now I see it.</p>

<p>I’m not broken for wanting to be nurtured.
I’m not weak for needing softness.
I’m just someone who never received it — and now knows how to name that wound.</p>

<p>And that changes everything.</p>

<p>Because if I can be conscious of the pattern, I don’t have to keep repeating it.
And if I can meet myself with compassion, I won’t need others to hold what I’m not willing to hold within.</p>

<p>I don’t need saving.
I don’t need fixing.
I just need truth. And care. And the kind of love that starts from within.</p>

<p>And that… I can give myself now.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Inner" /><category term="Child," /><category term="Relationships," /><category term="Shame," /><category term="Healing," /><category term="Self-Parenting" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I used to unconsciously search for a nurturing parent in others — and often found the critical one instead. Now I see the pattern clearly, and I’m learning to meet myself with the compassion I was never given.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Respecting the Edge</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/respecting-the-edge/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Respecting the Edge" /><published>2025-06-04T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-06-04T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/respecting-the-edge</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/respecting-the-edge/"><![CDATA[<p>I woke up at 3 a.m. today with only a few hours of sleep.<br />
By all accounts, I should be pushing through.<br />
Play poker. Clean the house. Be productive.<br />
That’s the script I was raised with — that if I’m not <em>doing</em>, I’m falling behind.</p>

<p>But I’ve been listening more closely to myself lately. And today, my body was saying: <em>rest.</em></p>

<p>Even though my body battery said 59%, I knew I was on fumes.<br />
So instead of powering through, I took a nap. I played one more short tournament.<br />
And then I stopped. Not out of laziness — but out of <em>respect</em>.</p>

<p>There’s something countercultural about that. Something that used to feel wrong.<br />
How could I want so much from life — a partner, peace, purpose — and still let myself <em>sit</em>?</p>

<p>But I’m learning.<br />
Learning that slowing down doesn’t mean giving up.<br />
Learning that trusting the process is the most radical thing I can do right now.</p>

<p>I want to be a great partner for someone one day.<br />
And I know I will be — because I’m learning to be that for <em>myself</em> first.<br />
Not just intellectually. But in action. In stillness. In how I choose to respond when I feel overwhelmed or alone.</p>

<p>I’ve made mistakes in the past — picked people who activated my wounds instead of helping them heal.<br />
People who felt like the nurturing parent I never had, but who turned out to be the critical voice I’ve spent my life trying to quiet.</p>

<p>And I see now — I was caught in the drama triangle:<br />
Victim. Rescuer. Persecutor.<br />
Switching roles. Staying stuck. Always dysregulated.</p>

<p>But today, I’m stepping out of the triangle.<br />
I’m choosing presence over performance.<br />
And that, in itself, is healing.</p>

<p>So I’m taking it slow.<br />
Not because I’ve lost faith in life.<br />
But because I’ve finally started to trust it.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Nervous" /><category term="System," /><category term="Self-Trust," /><category term="Rest," /><category term="Acceptance," /><category term="Relationships" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[A reflection on slowing down, letting go of old survival patterns, and building trust in the self again.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Measuring My Days Differently</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/measuring-my-days-differently/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Measuring My Days Differently" /><published>2025-06-04T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-06-04T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/measuring-my-days-differently</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/measuring-my-days-differently/"><![CDATA[<p>Body:</p>

<p>There’s a quiet shift happening in me.</p>

<p>I used to measure my days by how productive I was — how much I ticked off, how much I achieved, how well I kept up. But now I’m learning to measure my days differently.</p>

<p>I’m starting to measure them by how present I was.
By how in tune I was with myself.
By how little I abandoned who I really am.</p>

<p>That’s the real shift:
I’m not just trying to live this way anymore — I’m starting to actually believe in it.</p>

<p>I used to say things like, “Productivity doesn’t define me”, but deep down I didn’t fully buy it. There was always that background noise telling me I had to prove something. That I wasn’t enough unless I was doing more.</p>

<p>But now, more and more, something deeper in me is starting to trust that being here — being aligned, not rushing, not performing — that’s the actual point.</p>

<hr />

<p>And the strange thing is… I’m okay.</p>

<p>Not perfect. Not “healed.” But okay.</p>

<p>I don’t need to be saved.
And no one around me needs to be saved either.</p>

<p>If there’s a part of me that’s still hurting, still afraid, still unsure — I can meet it.
I can hold it.
I can be the one who shows up.</p>

<p>I don’t need to fix myself.
And I don’t need to fix anyone else.</p>

<hr />

<p>That feels like freedom.
A quiet kind of freedom.
Not a dramatic escape — just an honest returning.</p>

<p>I am free.
And so is everyone else.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Presence," /><category term="Healing," /><category term="Self-Trust," /><category term="Emotional" /><category term="Growth," /><category term="Freedom" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I used to measure my days by what I got done. Now I’m learning to measure them by how much I stayed with myself. No saving. No fixing. Just presence.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Listening to the Shadow</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/listening-to-the-shadow/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Listening to the Shadow" /><published>2025-06-04T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-06-04T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/listening-to-the-shadow</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/listening-to-the-shadow/"><![CDATA[<p>It’s just after midnight. My body battery was at 18 earlier—utterly drained. But now… I’m at 27. I haven’t done anything physically intense today. But emotionally? Yeah. I’ve been through a lot.</p>

<p>And oddly enough, I feel better now.<br />
Not because something outside changed, but because I finally sat down with myself. No distractions. No noise. Just me.</p>

<p>It hit me that maybe this exhaustion I’ve been feeling for years isn’t just about poor sleep or stress—maybe it’s the voice of my shadow self. Not a villain. Not some saboteur. But the younger parts of me crying out to be heard.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>“If I drain your energy… will you finally sit with me?”</p>
</blockquote>

<p>It’s not manipulation. It’s a survival strategy. The most sensitive, unseen parts of me found the only way to get attention: shut down everything else until I finally stop and listen.</p>

<p>And here’s the strange thing: when I do, I start to feel whole. It’s quiet, but it’s real.<br />
Not some dopamine rush from figuring something out. Not some insight to file away.<br />
Just <em>me</em>, being with <em>me</em>.</p>

<p>I’ve been neglecting that for a long time—especially when parenting. I love my son more than anything, but I’ve also felt tension there. Resentment even. Because being with him often requires me to put myself aside. And that’s hard when there are parts of me that are <em>begging</em> not to be put aside anymore.</p>

<p>So I’m starting to understand something:</p>

<p>This isn’t manipulation.<br />
This is a homecoming.</p>

<p>And maybe that’s enough for now. To know that, when I feel depleted… the answer isn’t always to push through.<br />
Sometimes, the answer is to <em>return</em>—to myself.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Healing," /><category term="Self-Compassion," /><category term="Integration," /><category term="Shadow" /><category term="Work," /><category term="Parenting" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if the exhaustion isn’t burnout—but a call from within?]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Learning to Allow</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/learning-to-allow/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Learning to Allow" /><published>2025-06-04T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-06-04T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/learning-to-allow</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/learning-to-allow/"><![CDATA[<p>Body:</p>

<p>I keep coming back to this idea of uncertainty — not as something to conquer, but something to be with.</p>

<p>It’s been difficult for me to move into that way of being. Most of my life has been shaped by the need to control. To manage. To preempt. I’ve never really had someone model what it looks like to trust the process. It was always about survival, never surrender.
It was always out of fear.</p>

<p>But I’m starting to ease into a different kind of framework.</p>

<p>What if it could come from love?
What if I could trust the process — not out of naivety or false optimism, but because I finally believe that the life I want doesn’t have to be forced into place?</p>

<p>That maybe the most fruitful things in life grow slowly. Quietly.
Only when given space.</p>

<hr />

<p>It’s still hard.
Letting things naturally arise. Not rushing into conversations, relationships, or plans just to fill a gap. Not gripping onto meaning in every moment.</p>

<p>But I’m learning that trying to force life to bend to my timeline has only kept me from noticing the life already trying to meet me.</p>

<p>There’s something deeper available in the waiting.
A freedom I’ve never really known.</p>

<hr />

<p>And maybe, if I keep choosing this —
If I allow things to unfold without control —
The people who are meant to walk with me will find me.
Naturally.
Without force.
Without pretending.
Without me having to exhaust myself to earn it.</p>

<p>Just me, showing up — open, rooted, and finally letting life come to me.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Healing," /><category term="Uncertainty," /><category term="Trust," /><category term="Self-Growth," /><category term="Emotional" /><category term="Regulation" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moving from fear to trust is difficult — but it might be where most of the fruit is. A quiet reflection on letting life unfold without force.]]></summary></entry></feed>