<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-05-31T13:36:41+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Embracing Authenticity</title><subtitle>A space to grow, reflect, and be your true self.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Why I’m Not Forcing Connection Anymore</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/why-im-not-forcing-connection-anymore.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why I’m Not Forcing Connection Anymore" /><published>2025-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/why-im-not-forcing-connection-anymore</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/why-im-not-forcing-connection-anymore.html"><![CDATA[<p>There’s a big difference between <em>seeking connection</em> and <em>forcing it</em>. I used to blur that line. I’d try to make something happen—start conversations, hold space, extend myself—just to feel a sense of closeness, even if the energy wasn’t mutual.</p>

<p>These days, I’ve stopped chasing. I say hello. I show up. I remain open. But I don’t twist myself into something I’m not just to fit into someone else’s world.</p>

<p>And it’s freeing.</p>

<p>It means I can walk my dog and smile at a stranger without expecting anything back. I can message someone once without spiraling if they don’t respond. I can go to the gym, or a class, or the sauna, and just enjoy being around people without needing to be <em>chosen</em>.</p>

<p>Connection that’s forced never lasts. It comes from a place of fear. But when it flows naturally, it feels safe, reciprocal, and steady.</p>

<p>I’m learning to let relationships unfold without trying to script the ending. I’m learning to let silence speak. I’m learning that the people who are meant to connect with me—really connect—won’t need convincing.</p>

<p>And in the meantime, I’m choosing peace over pursuit.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Connection means more when it happens naturally.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">I Dont Need To Rush My Journey</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/i-dont-need-to-rush-my-journey.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I Dont Need To Rush My Journey" /><published>2025-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/i-dont-need-to-rush-my-journey</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/i-dont-need-to-rush-my-journey.html"><![CDATA[<p>This is the markdown content for post titled: <em>I Dont Need To Rush My Journey</em>.</p>

<p>This post was written from the perspective of a man learning to heal, grow, and live more authentically—one day at a time.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authentic reflection from a personal journey of healing and growth.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">When You Realise It Was Never Your Job to Fix Them</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/when-you-realise-it-was-never-your-job-to-fix-them.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="When You Realise It Was Never Your Job to Fix Them" /><published>2025-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/when-you-realise-it-was-never-your-job-to-fix-them</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/when-you-realise-it-was-never-your-job-to-fix-them.html"><![CDATA[<p>Someone messaged me recently after months of silence—straight into their struggles, asking for help. No real “How are you?” No curiosity about what’s been happening in my world.</p>

<p>Just more of the same.</p>

<p>And for a long time, I would’ve dropped everything. I would’ve stayed up late, listened deeply, offered insight, and carried the emotional weight for both of us.</p>

<p>But I don’t do that anymore.</p>

<p>It’s not because I don’t care. I care deeply. But I’m no longer willing to be the go-to therapist for people who don’t even ask how I’m doing.</p>

<p>I used to feel guilty about that shift. Like I was abandoning people. But I’ve realised: it was never my job to fix anyone. Especially people who never held space for me in return.</p>

<p>These kinds of friendships aren’t balanced. They’re extractive.</p>

<p>Now, I pause before responding. I check in with myself first. Am I willing to give this energy? Will this be reciprocal? Will I leave this conversation feeling seen too?</p>

<p>If not, I step back.</p>

<p>Boundaries don’t mean I don’t care. They mean I finally care about myself, too.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was playing therapist in so many friendships—and it drained me.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">When Someone Doesn’t Choose Me</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/when-someone-doesnt-choose-me.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="When Someone Doesn’t Choose Me" /><published>2025-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/when-someone-doesnt-choose-me</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/when-someone-doesnt-choose-me.html"><![CDATA[<p>There’s a sting that comes when someone doesn’t choose me.</p>

<p>When I show up open, honest, willing—and it’s not met. When I feel something real, and they… don’t. Or maybe they do, but not enough to stay. Not enough to try.</p>

<p>And for a long time, I made that mean something about <em>me</em>.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>“You’re not enough.”<br />
“You were too much.”<br />
“You scared them off.”<br />
“You did it wrong.”</p>
</blockquote>

<p>But the truth is—<strong>their decision isn’t a measure of my worth.</strong></p>

<p>People walk away for all kinds of reasons that have nothing to do with who I am. And sometimes, rejection is just redirection wrapped in pain.</p>

<p>I can grieve it.<br />
I can feel it.<br />
But I don’t have to carry it as a reflection of my value.</p>

<p>I am still loveable.<br />
I am still growing.<br />
I am still becoming.</p>

<p>And the right people?<br />
They won’t need convincing.</p>

<p>They’ll choose me freely—because they <em>want</em> to.</p>

<p>Until then, I’ll keep choosing myself.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[It hurts—but it doesn’t mean I’m not worthy of being chosen.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">When I’m Triggered by Kindness</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/when-im-triggered-by-kindness.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="When I’m Triggered by Kindness" /><published>2025-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/when-im-triggered-by-kindness</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/when-im-triggered-by-kindness.html"><![CDATA[<p>It caught me off guard the first time it happened.</p>

<p>Someone was kind to me—gently, sincerely—and my body tensed up. I wanted to trust it, but I also wanted to run. Something in me whispered:</p>
<blockquote>
  <p>“What do they want?”<br />
“This won’t last.”<br />
“Be careful.”</p>
</blockquote>

<p>I wasn’t used to kindness without strings.<br />
I wasn’t used to softness that didn’t lead to pain.</p>

<p>And it made me realise—<strong>I wasn’t triggered by the person. I was triggered by what kindness used to mean.</strong></p>

<p>Because in the past, it often came just before the drop.<br />
Before the withdrawal. The criticism. The confusion.</p>

<p>But now, I’m letting myself learn something new.</p>

<p>Kindness can be safe.<br />
Gentle people exist.<br />
Not everyone who leans in is preparing to walk away.</p>

<p>It takes time.<br />
It takes regulation.<br />
It takes patience with the parts of me that still brace for harm.</p>

<p>But I’m learning.</p>

<p>And slowly, I’m letting kindness feel like home again.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes kindness feels unfamiliar—and that’s okay.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">When I Feel the Urge to Chase</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/when-i-feel-the-urge-to-chase.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="When I Feel the Urge to Chase" /><published>2025-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/when-i-feel-the-urge-to-chase</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/when-i-feel-the-urge-to-chase.html"><![CDATA[<p>There are moments when I feel the urge to chase.</p>

<p>Chase a message. Chase a connection. Chase validation. Chase the feeling that I matter.</p>

<p>And when that urge rises, it’s loud. It feels urgent. Like I <em>need</em> to act on it immediately or I’ll lose something forever.</p>

<p>But I’m starting to slow down and ask:</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>“What am I really chasing right now?”</p>
</blockquote>

<p>More often than not, it’s not the person or situation in front of me—it’s a feeling I didn’t get somewhere else. An old unmet need. A version of me still waiting to be chosen.</p>

<p>So I pause.</p>

<p>I breathe.</p>

<p>And I remind myself:</p>
<ul>
  <li>If it’s real, I won’t have to chase it.</li>
  <li>If it’s mutual, I won’t have to convince anyone.</li>
  <li>If it’s meant, it will meet me halfway.</li>
</ul>

<p>This is how I’m unlearning pursuit as proof of worth.</p>

<p>This is how I’m letting myself <em>be chosen</em>—without performing, pleasing, or proving.</p>

<p>And some days, that choice changes everything.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The desire to pursue often comes from an old wound, not a present truth.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What My Triggered Self Needs to Hear</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/what-my-triggered-self-needs-to-hear.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What My Triggered Self Needs to Hear" /><published>2025-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/what-my-triggered-self-needs-to-hear</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/what-my-triggered-self-needs-to-hear.html"><![CDATA[<p>When I’m triggered, advice doesn’t land.</p>

<p>It doesn’t help to be told “just let it go” or “you’re safe now.” Even my own well-meaning reminders can feel hollow in the middle of a reaction.</p>

<p>What I need in those moments isn’t logic. It’s <strong>presence</strong>.</p>

<p>A soft voice. A grounded energy. A reminder that I’m not wrong or broken or failing—I’m just in a part of me that’s overwhelmed. That part needs <em>comfort</em>, not correction.</p>

<p>Here’s what I try to tell myself now:</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>“Hey. I see you.<br />
This is old.<br />
You’re safe now, but it makes sense that it doesn’t feel that way.<br />
You’re not too much.<br />
You’re just feeling a lot.<br />
Let’s breathe through it together.”</p>
</blockquote>

<p>That voice? That’s the one I’m practicing.</p>

<p>Because healing isn’t about never being triggered.<br />
It’s about who meets me in that moment—especially when that person is me.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the heat of the moment, logic doesn’t help—but presence does.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What I Wanted Wasn’t Too Much</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/what-i-wanted-wasnt-too-much.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What I Wanted Wasn’t Too Much" /><published>2025-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/what-i-wanted-wasnt-too-much</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/what-i-wanted-wasnt-too-much.html"><![CDATA[<p>For a long time, I carried this fear:</p>
<blockquote>
  <p>“Maybe I want too much.”<br />
Too much depth. Too much honesty. Too much emotional safety. Too much presence.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>I shrank parts of myself to avoid being “intense.” I watered down my truth to be easier to digest. I lowered the volume of my needs—hoping someone would notice me without me having to speak.</p>

<p>But here’s what I’ve come to realise:</p>

<p><strong>What I wanted wasn’t too much.</strong><br />
It just wasn’t available in the places I kept searching.</p>

<p>And that’s not a flaw in me. It’s a misalignment.</p>

<p>Now I’m unlearning the belief that asking for what I truly need is a burden. I’m unlearning the reflex to apologise for longing. I’m unlearning the idea that needing depth means I’m too sensitive.</p>

<p>What I wanted was never too much.<br />
It just requires someone who knows how to meet it.</p>

<p>And while I wait, I’ve learned to meet myself that way too.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[It just wasn’t met by the right people.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trusting Slow Burns Over Sudden Sparks</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/trusting-slow-burns-over-sudden-sparks.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trusting Slow Burns Over Sudden Sparks" /><published>2025-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/trusting-slow-burns-over-sudden-sparks</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/trusting-slow-burns-over-sudden-sparks.html"><![CDATA[<p>I used to chase the spark.</p>

<p>That instant connection. The rush of being seen. The intensity that made everything else fade away.</p>

<p>It felt like love—but often, it was a nervous system high. A collision of unmet needs. A flare that burned bright and fast, but rarely lasted.</p>

<p>Now, I’m learning to trust the <em>slow burn</em>.</p>

<p>The kind that starts quietly. Where safety builds gradually. Where mutual effort replaces emotional fireworks. Where I don’t feel a need to prove or perform.</p>

<p>Slow burns grow stronger with time.<br />
They’re based in consistency, not chaos.<br />
They feel like warmth—not wildfire.</p>

<p>It’s a different kind of excitement. More grounded. More sustainable.</p>

<p>And I’m starting to see that the relationships worth keeping often begin this way—not with a bang, but with a steady light I learn to trust.</p>

<p>That’s what I’m open to now.</p>

<p>Not intensity.<br />
But intimacy.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I used to crave instant chemistry. Now, I look for steady warmth.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Version of Me I’m Becoming Is Worth the Wait</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/the-version-of-me-im-becoming-is-worth-the-wait.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Version of Me I’m Becoming Is Worth the Wait" /><published>2025-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2025-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/the-version-of-me-im-becoming-is-worth-the-wait</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/05/31/the-version-of-me-im-becoming-is-worth-the-wait.html"><![CDATA[<p>Sometimes I wonder if I’m taking too long.</p>

<p>If I should be further along. Clearer. Braver. More consistent. Less triggered. More “healed.”</p>

<p>But then I breathe—and remember:</p>

<p><strong>Becoming takes time.</strong></p>

<p>Real change isn’t linear.<br />
It happens slowly, then all at once.<br />
It’s found in the pauses. The setbacks. The quiet moments no one sees.</p>

<p>And the version of me I’m becoming?</p>

<p>He’s learning to rest.<br />
To trust himself.<br />
To say no with ease.<br />
To walk away when it hurts—even if he still loves.</p>

<p>She’s not rushing anymore.<br />
She’s growing on purpose.</p>

<p>And she knows that slow doesn’t mean stuck.</p>

<p>It means <em>rooted</em>.</p>

<p>I’m not behind—I’m in bloom.</p>

<p>Even if no one else sees it yet.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not everything blooms fast. Some transformations take their time—and that’s okay.]]></summary></entry></feed>